cashinonbanners.com 2019-05-26

# Cash In On Banners

**Cash In On Banners** (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the http://cashinonbanners.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

 **Information Collection And Use:**  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email and name   
(“Personal Information”).

**Log data**  
We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

**Cookies:**

We use “cookies” (files with small amount of data) to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

**Security:  
**The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
  
**Links To Other Sites:  
** Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy:**

We reserve the right to change these terms at any time. You must comply with any new changes to these terms within 7 days of their posting on our website.

**Contacting us:**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: office@cashinonbanners.com
